mysoju.com 2008-12-16

# Watch Korean, Japanese, Taiwanese Drama and Movie online!

### MySoju.com Privacy Policy

MySoju.com is committed to protecting your privacy. MySoju.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. MySoju.com will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. The following contains details on how we treat all information collected on MySoju.com

#### Your Acceptance

BY USING AND/OR VISITING THIS WEBSITE (collectively, including all Content available through the MySoju.com domain name, the "MySoju Website", or "Website"), YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO TERMS OF USE, WHICH ARE PUBLISHED AT http://www.mysoju.com/policy/, AND WHICH ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE. If you do not agree to any of these terms, then please do not use the MySoju.com Website.

#### Personal Information

#### All Users Activity

Any User can use MySoju.com without having a MySoju.com Account or any other Account.

#### Usage Information

We may record information about your usage, such as when you use MySoju.com, how many times you visit the website and other non-personal identifiable information.

#### Uses

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through MySoju.com, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of MySoju.com, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major MySoju.com changes).

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of MySoju.com and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.

We use cookies and log file information to:   
(1) provide custom, personalized content and information;   
(2) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns;   
(3) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, time on site, bounce rate, etc...   

#### Links sent to MySoju.com

Any link that you voluntarily send us becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

#### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

MySoju.com allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within MySoju.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on MySoju.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

MySoju.com does not provide any personally identifiable information to third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.
